

Dwi Putra Bayu Oktantyo

UI/UX Designer | Web Designer | Front-End Specialist

- +62 89604333574
- dwiputrabayu.rf.gd
- OKI Jakarta, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

Junior Programmer Beauty World

04/2022 - 08/2022

Fix the appearance of the website when it is openend on the desktop or on the mobile, add soft delete on each field, create an activitylog for the website, create a search feature by store name, create an api filter for purchase history, change the api data type.

Website: www.beemall.id

Junior Programmer GORGA GROUP

06/2020 - 09/2020

Creating websites from scratch for corporate project. Starting with buying hosting, creating template, building a website with Laravel, uploading hosting, setting up SSL& website pagespeed.

Website: www.pusatnusa.com

Junior Programmer

Cooperative Sejahtera Mandiri

01/2017 - 06/2017

Create a mobile application for cooperatives. Make a splash screen to enter the application, make the homapage menu display on the mobile, make the display on each menu in the application.

EDUCATION

System Information Mercu Buana University

2019

Bachelor of System Information

Creating a web application for a Dokter Bersama Clinic.

SUMMARY

Experienced Operational Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. I am skilled in web design and UI/UX Designer. I mastered tool figma for create mock up and microsoft office for office administration. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer/Information Technology from Mercu Buana University. Portfolio -> http://dwiputrabayu.rf.gd

SKILLS

Figma Intermediate Adobe XD Beginner Beginner **InVision HTML** Intermediate CSS Intermediate Javascript Beginner Intermediate Communication **Design Thinking** Intermediate Creativity Intermediate Problem Solving Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Fluent

English Intermediate